Guide to the Richard Maass Collection of Westchester and New York State 1645-1995, (Bulk: 1645-1910) MSS.055
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Westchester
  - Subseries A: Letters and Documents
    - creator: Richardson, James place: Kingsbridge, Sep 27, 1776; 055-002-a-0311 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      dimensions: 19cm x 12cm
      Receipt for barrels of pork distributed from the magazine
    - creator: Bushnell, Jonathan place: Rye, Sep 29, 1776; 055-002-a-0293 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for 150 Continental dollars
    - creator: Richardson, James place: Kingsbridge, Sep 30, 1776; 055-002-a-0365 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Receipt for rum distributed from the magazine
    - creator: Laurence, John., Sep 8, 1776; 055-002-a-0290 (Box 5, Folder 17)
      physical description: Receipt; d.s.
      dimensions: 21cm x 12cm
    - creator: Clift, Waterman place: New York, Aug 24, 1776; 055-002-a-0413; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 18)
      dimensions: 18cm x 7cm
      Receipt for six pounds seven shillings from Captain Isaac Gallop
    - creator: Marchant, John place: s.l., Jan 10, 1776; 055-002-a-0410; 1 pages (Box 5, Folder 18)
      dimensions: 16cm x 10cm
      declaration of enlistment through end of December 1776, signed by John Marchant and Josiah Woodworth
    - creator: Spencer, Joseph, 1714-1789 place: s.l., Mar 26, 1776; 055-002-a-0411; 1 pages (Box 5, Folder 18)
      dimensions: 11cm x 12cm
      muster list of six men signed by Brigadier-General Spencer, Captain Isaac Gallop at head of list
    - creator: Eldridge, Charles place: New York, May 25, 1776; 055-002-a-0416; 1 pages (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Receipt for three pounds twelve shillings from Captain Isaac Gallop
    - creator: Mathes, Samuel place: s.l., May 31, 1776; 055-002-a-0412; 1 pages (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Receipt for forty pounds four shillings from Captain Isaac Gallop
    - creator: Van Cortlandt, Pierre place: New York, Jan 11, 1776; 055-002-a-0417; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 19)
      physical description: folded full sheet with wax fragments, multiple repairs; l. s.
      To Robert R. Livingston, Jr. As Chairman of the Committee of Safety, Van Cortlandt writes regarding the erection of a powder mill now that saltpeter is available.
    - creator: Fish, Nicholas, 1758-1833 place: New York, Apr 9, 1776; 055-002-a-0420; 4 pages (Box 5, Folder 20)
      physical description: folded half sheet, multiple repairs; a.l.s.
      To Captain Richard Varick. Regarding the spiking of cannons in Westchester.
    - creator: Reed, Joseph, 1741-1785 place: Manhattan, Jul 1, 1776; 055-002-a-0425; 1 pages (Box 5, Folder 21)
      physical description: fragment of sheet trimmed and mounted; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 19cm x 20cm
      To the New York Provincial Congress. Requesting lead for bullets.
    - creator: Woodhull, Nathaniel, 1722-1776 place: White Plains, Jul 12, 1776; 055-002-a-0426; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 22)
      physical description: fragment of half sheet, silked; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 21cm x 23cm
      To the Commanding Officer 'at the fortifications in the highlands'A warning of enemy ships' activity on the Hudson, signed by Woodhull in his capacity as President of the New York Convention.
    - creator: Broome, John, 1738-1810 place: White Plains, Jul 16, 1776; 055-002-a-0429; 1 pages (Box 5, Folder 23)
      Request to commission the Sloop Independence as a privateer.
    - creator: Livingston, Gilbert place: Poughkeepsie, Jul 25, 1776; 055-002-a-0430; 1 pages (Box 5, Folder 24)
      physical description: folded full sheet, silked; a.l.s.
      To Peter Curtineus. Order to place a chain across the Hudson River. Also signed by William Paulding.
    - creator: Jay, John, 1745-1829 place: [Connecticut], Jul 29, 1776; 055-002-a-0431; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 25)
      physical description: folded half sheet with wax fragments; a. l. s
      To Sally [Sarah Jay] at General Livingstone's in Elizabeth Town, New Jersey
    - creator: McKesson, John place: Harlem, Aug 24, 1776; 055-002-a-0434; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 26)
      physical description: fragment trimmed and mounted; a. d.s.
      dimensions: 19cm x 26cm
      Money is ordered to be paid to Hugh Doyle, a soldier who escaped from a British prison camp, on the reverse is Doyle's acknowledgment of receipt of payment.
    - creator: Hand, Edward, 1744-1802 place: New York, Aug 30, 1776; 055-002-a-0437; 1 pages (Box 5, Folder 27)
      physical description: folded half sheet with wax seal; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 21cm x 29cm
      To Dearest Kitty (his wife) Reports the capture of General John Sullivan and General Sterling.
    - creator: Reed, Joseph, 1741-1785 place: Head Quarters, Oct 7, 1776; 055-002-a-0438; 1 pages (Box 5, Folder 28)
      To Governor George Clinton. Removal northward of Governor Clinton's baggage.
    - creator: Huntington, Joshua place: [Kingsbridge], Oct 12, 1776; 055-002-a-0439; 1 pages (Box 5, Folder 29)
      To Andrew Huntington.
    - creator: Livingston, Robert place: [New York], Oct 12, 1776; 055-002-a-0440; 5 pages (Box 5, Folder 30)
      physical description: three half sheets, two masure 19cm x 31, third measures 19cm x 24cm; Draft a. l.
      To George Washington. Suggestions for disposition of American troops in defense of New York City.
    - creator: Washington, George, 1732-1799 place: Harlem Heights, Oct 13, 1776; 055-002-a-0446; 3 pages (Box 5, Folder 31)
      physical description: folded half sheet, multiple repairs; l. s.
      To Artemas Ward. Reports that 'yesterday the enemy landed at Frogs Point.' Body in hand of Robert Hanson Harrison, signed by Washington.
    - creator: Smallwood, William, 1732-1792 place: Phillips Heights, Oct 17, 1776; 055-002-a-0450; 8 pages (Box 5, Folder 32)
      physical description: two half sheets folded and quired; a.l.s.
      To the Maryland Provincial Congress.
    - creator: Northumberland, Hugh Percy, Duke of, 1742-1817 place: New York, Oct 24, 1776; 055-002-a-0459; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 33)
      physical description: fragment trimmed and mounted.; a.l.s.
      To Thomas Percy.
    - creator: Clinton, George, 1739-1812 place: Camp near White Plains, Oct 29, 1776; 055-002-a-0462; 3 pages (Box 5, Folder 34)
      physical description: folded full sheet, multiple repairs; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 39cm x 33cm
      To John McKesson. Describes the Battle of White Plains.
    - creator: Putnam, Philip place: Raged Hills (Connecticut), Nov 2, 1776; 055-002-a-0466; 1 pages (Box 5, Folder 35)
      physical description: fragment; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 18cm x 21cm
      To Jonathan Livemore. Describes the battle of White Plains.
    - creator: Trumbull, Joseph, 1737-1778 place: North Castle, Nov 17, 1776; 055-002-a-0467; 2 pages (Box 5, Folder 36)
      dimensions: 20cm x 26cm
    - creator: Wooster, David, 1711-1777 place: Saw Pitts, Nov 18, 1776; 055-002-a-0470; 1 pages (Box 5, Folder 37)
      physical description: fragment, trimmed and mounted; a. n. s.
      A copy of letter to Major St. John requesting the procurement of gun powder.
    - creator: Trumbull, Joseph, 1737-1778 place: North Castle, Nov 26, 1776; 055-002-a-0471; 3 pages (Box 5, Folder 38)
      physical description: folded full sheet with wax fragments; a.l.s.
      To Elbridge Gerry
    - creator: Clinton, George, 1739-1812 place: Fort Constitution, Dec 2, 1776; 055-002-a-0475; 1 pages (Box 5, Folder 39)
      dimensions: 22cm x 24cm
      Military orders.
    - creator: Wyllys, George place: Middletown, Connecticut, Dec 18, 1776; 055-002-a-0476; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 40)
      Payment for troops who marched to the relief of General Washington at New York.
    - creator: Wyllys, George. place: Middletown, Connecticut, Dec 31, 1776; 055-002-a-0477; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 41)
      dimensions: 17cm x 20cm
      Connecticut pay order.
    - creator: Chittenden, Gideon place: [Peekskill], Various dates; 055-002-a-0478; 6 pages (Box 6, Folder 42)
      physical description: 2 folded fragments; Orderly book
      Orderly book kept by Gideon Chittenden in the Connecticut Regiment under Colonel Noadiah Hooker.
    - creator: Account of execution of a traitor. place: [near Peekskill], 1777; 055-002-a-0485; 6 pages (Box 6, Folder 43)
      physical description: 3 leaves sewn in a gathering, 1 inserted leaf.; chapbook
      dimensions: 21cm x 18cm
      A contemporary account of the execution of Daniel Strang.
    - creator: Duer, William, 1747-1799. place: Peekskill, Jan 3, 1777; 055-002-a-0492; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 44)
      physical description: half sheet in folio; a.l.s.
      To John Jay.
    - creator: Huntington, Ebenezer, 1754-1834. place: Peekskill, Jan 5, 1777; 055-002-a-0495; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 45)
      To Joshua Huntington.
    - creator: Backus, Ebenezer. place: Hartford, Connecticut, Jan 13, 1777; 055-002-a-0496; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 46)
      dimensions: 19cm x 13cm
      Receipt of pay for 'troops of light' who marched to New York in September.
    - creator: Ellsworth, Oliver, 1745-1807. place: [Hartford], Mar 21, 1777; 055-002-a-0497; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 47)
      Payment to Captain Silas Dunham for clothing lost in retreat from New York.
    - creator: Shoat, Jesse place: Hartford, Apr 25, 1777; 055-002-a-0500; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 48)
      dimensions: 22cm x 14cm
      To John Laurence, Treasurer. Order for payment for Isaac Phelps.
    - creator: Shoat, Jesse place: Canaan, May 19, 1777; 055-002-a-0501; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 48)
      To John Laurence, Treasurer. Order of payment for Captain Timothy Moses.
    - creator: Webb, Charles. place: Stamford, Connecticut, May 13, 1777; 055-002-a-0502; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 49)
      physical description: half sheet, trimmed; d.s.
      dimensions: 21cm x 28cm
      Copy of record from Connecticut pay table relating to Joseph Chilton, a soldier who was wounded in the Battle of White Plains.
    - creator: Drake, Samuel, fl. 1778-1779. place: New York, May 17, 1777; 055-002-a-0503; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 50)
      dimensions: 21cm x 16cm
      Receipt of payment for various expenses incurred as Commissioner for Westchester County, signed by Drake.
    - creator: Van Cortlandt, Pierre. place: Kingston, May 21, 1777; 055-002-a-0504; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 51)
      physical description: 2 half sheets, wax fragments; a.l.s.
      To General Alexander McDougal.
    - creator: Visscher, Matthew. place: Albany, May 30, 1777; 055-002-a-0505; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 52)
      Payment for John Bleecker's attendance at various Conventions. Docketed.
    - creator: Ellsworth, Oliver, 1745-1807. place: Hartford, Jun 3, 1777; 055-002-a-0506; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 53)
      dimensions: 22cm x 16cm
      Payment to General Israel Putnam for clothing lost in retreat from New York.
    - creator: Ellsworth, Oliver, 1745-1807. place: [Hartford], Jun 6, 1777; 055-002-a-0509; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 54)
      To John Lawrence, Treasurer. Order of payment to Ebenezar Coe.
    - creator: Pratt, Thomas. place: Hartford, Jun 18, 1777; 055-002-a-0510; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 55)
      physical description: half sheet, extensive repairs; a.l.s.
      To his sisters. Description of Pratt's troubles as a refugee.
    - creator: Mumford, Giles. place: Peekskill, Jul 19, 1777; 055-002-a-0513; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 56)
      dimensions: 17cm x 22cm
      To Thomas Mumford. Regarding an exchange of prisoners.
    - creator: Sullivan, John, 1740-1795. place: Headquarters, Cortlandt Manor, Jul 25, 1777; 055-002-a-0516; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 57)
      physical description: full sheet in folio; a. d.s.
      dimensions: 22cm x 34cm
      Remittance of a death sentence.
    - creator: Mumford, Giles. place: Crompond, Jul 27, 1777; 055-002-a-0517; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 58)
      dimensions: 32cm x 21cm
      To Thomas Mumford.
    - creator: Wadsworth, Jeremiah,1743-1804. place: Peekskill, Aug 9, 1777; 055-002-a-0520; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 59)
      To Captain Nehemiah Hubbard.
    - creator: Mills, John. place: Peekskill, Aug 17, 1777; 055-002-a-0523; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 60)
      Receipt for blankets.
    - creator: Putnam, Israel, 1718-1790. place: Peekskill, Sep 7, 1777; 055-002-a-0524; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 61)
      physical description: full sheet in folio; l. s.
      dimensions: 42cm x 32cm
      To Colonel Jeremiah Wadsworth.
    - creator: Putnam, Israel, 1718-1790. place: Peekskill, Sep 29, 1777; 055-002-a-0525; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 62)
      physical description: half sheet; l. s.
      Copy of letter to George Washington.
    - creator: Washington, George, 1732-1799. place: Skippock Camp, Oct 11, 1777; 055-002-a-0526; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 63)
      physical description: fragment; l. s.
      dimensions: 20cm x 25cm
      To Israel Putnam.
    - creator: Huntington, Jabez, 1719-1786. place: Albany, Oct 18, 1777; 055-002-a-0527; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 64)
      dimensions: 31cm x 35cm
    - creator: Putnam, Israel, 1718-1790. place: Headquarters, Fishkill, Nov 1, 1777; 055-002-a-0528; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 65)
      dimensions: 19cm x 18cm
      To Colonel Gilbert Drake
    - creator: Webb, Samuel Blachley, 1753-1807. place: King Street, Nov 8, 1777; 055-002-a-0529; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 66)
      physical description: full sheet, wax fragments; a.l.s.
    - creator: Newell, Timothy. place: Scarsdale, Nov 20, 1777; 055-002-a-0530; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 67)
      dimensions: 15cm x 6cm
      Order for rum.
    - creator: Fishbourne, Benjamin, d. 1819. place: Wrights Mills, Jul 20, 1778; 055-002-a-0531 (Box 6, Folder 68)
      physical description: octavo bound volume, several signatures cut out at end. Paper boards with leather spine and corners.; Orderly book
      extent: [107] pages
      Orderly book of Major Fishbourne, begun at Wrights Mills, July 20, 1778. Last entry from September 1778.
    - creator: Parsons, Samuel Holden, 1737-1789. place: [Fishkill], Feb 9, 1778; 055-002-a-0532; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 69)
      physical description: half sheet with wax fragments; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 19cm x 31 cm
    - creator: Blakman, Elijah place: White Plains, Jun 1778; 055-002-a-0535; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 70)
      physical description: full sheet; d.s.
      A muster roll of Captain Elijah Blackman's company in Colonel Henry Sherburne's batalion. Signed by Samuel H. Parsons. Docketed.
    - creator: Martin, Robert. place: s.l., Jun 22, 1778; 055-002-a-0539; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 71)
      physical description: half sheet, partially printed; d.s.
      Bond posted for recruiting men in Connecticut. Signed by Robert Martin, et. al.
    - creator: Ensign, John. place: s.l., Jun 17, 1778; 055-002-a-0538; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 71)
      dimensions: 21cm x 35cm
      Bond posted for recruiting men in Connecticut. Signed by John Ensign and Fenn Wadsworth.
    - creator: Meigs, Return Jonathan, 1740-1823. place: White Plains, Jul 3, 1778; 055-002-a-0540; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 72)
      Receipt for 'lin. overhalls.'
    - creator: Sheldon, Elisha, 1740-1805. place: White Plains, Jul 10, 1778; 055-002-a-0541; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 73)
      dimensions: 20cm x 34cm
      Muster Roll of 2nd Regiment Light Dragoons.
    - creator: Gates, Horatio, 1728-1806. place: White Plains, Jul 12, 1778; 055-002-a-0542; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 74)
      Letter of explanation for the conduct of Colonel Hughes.
    - creator: Bride, James M., et al. place: White Plains, Jul 19, 1778; 055-002-a-0543; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 75)
      dimensions: 21cm x 34cm
      Complaint against an officer signed by soldiers in an artillery regiment of the line.
    - creator: Washington, George, 1732-1799. place: White Plains, Jul 21, 1778; 055-002-a-0544; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 76)
      To George Clinton, regarding Ethan Allen's political prisoners.
    - creator: Varick, Richard place: White Plains, Jul 22, 1778; 055-002-a-0547; 3 pages (Box 6, Folder 77)
      Muster roll of Colonel Dubois's regiment. Signed by Richard Varick.
    - creator: Clinton, James. place: White Plains, Jul 22, 1778; 055-002-a-0551; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 78)
      Muster roll of Capt. James Rosekrans' company in the Fifth New York regiment. Also signed by Richard Varick.
    - creator: Greene, Nathanael, 1742-1786. place: White Plains, Jul 23, 1778; 055-002-a-0554; 1 pages (Box 6, Folder 79)
      physical description: half sheet; l.
      dimensions: 24cm x 41cm
      To Nehemiah Hubbard.
    - creator: Washington, George, 1732-1799. place: White Plains, Jul 27, 1778; 055-002-a-0555; 2 pages (Box 6, Folder 80)
      physical description: full sheet; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 47cm x 38cm
      Plans for working with the French on Rhode Island campaign.
    - creator: Wadsworth, Jeremiah, 1743-1804. place: Harrison's Purchase, Jul 29, 1778; 055-002-a-0558; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 81)
      Share in a ship sold to Benjamin Tallmadge.
    - creator: Laurens, Henry, 1724-1792. place: Philadelphia, Jul 30, 1778; 055-002-a-0559; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 82)
      To William Palfrey.
    - creator: Washington, George, 1732-1799. place: White Plains, Aug 3, 1778; 055-002-a-0560; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 83)
      To Colonel Baylor.
    - creator: De Kalb, Johann, 1721-1780. place: White Plains, Aug 6, 1778; 055-002-a-0561; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 84)
      dimensions: 22cm x 26cm
      Oath of office of Lewis Woodruff. Signed by DeKalb.
    - creator: Philips, Frederick. place: New York, Aug 8, 1778; 055-002-a-0562; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 85)
      dimensions: 24cm x 14cm
      Financial document regarding Jonathan Budd.
    - creator: Varick, Richard, 1753-1831. place: White Plains, Aug 8, 1778; 055-002-a-0563; 5 pages (Box 7, Folder 86)
      physical description: two full sheets; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 42cm x 34cm
      To Colonel Joseph Ward.
    - creator: Washington, George, 1732-1799. place: White Plains, Aug 13, 1778; 055-002-a-0569; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 87)
      physical description: full sheet; l. s.
      dimensions: 41cm x 35cm
      To William Patterson. Request for Patterson to participate in the trial of Major General St. Clair.
    - creator: Scammell, Alexander, 1747-1781. place: West Point, Aug 18, 1778; 055-002-a-0570; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 88)
      A sickness leave for Ezra Badlam signed by Alexander Scammell on behalf of Washington.
    - creator: Varnum, James M. (James Mitchell), 1748-1789. place: [White Plains], Aug 27, 1778; 055-002-a-0571; 2 pages (Box 7, Folder 89)
      Leaf from an orderly book recording the court martial of Thomas Quigley.
    - creator: Phillips, Simon place: Slotts, Aug 16, 1779; 055-002-a-0575; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 90)
      To "My Lord" [John Fisher?] regarding movement of supplies.
    - creator: Sargent, Winthrop place: Camp Main Army, Aug 3, [1780]; 055-002-a-0580; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 90)
      physical description: half sheet, folded; d.s.
      dimensions: 33cm x 22cm
      To John Fisher at Fish Kill Langing.
    - creator: Wiltse, Martin place: Landing, Jan 4, 1781; 055-002-a-0579; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 90)
      To John Fisher regarding meeting with Israel Sniffin, Peter Thelletass, Abraham Philips and Cornelius Sebring to coordinate gathering wood.
    - creator: Sheafe, Henry place: Wapen Creek, Jul 11, 1781; 055-002-a-0581; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 90)
      Request for nails and chalk. Addressed to John Fisher.
    - creator: Sheafe, Henry place: Wapen Creek, Jul 22, 1781; 055-002-a-0582; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 90)
      dimensions: 23cm x 9cm
      Request for "Junck". Addressed to John Fisher.
    - creator: Campbell, John place: Contel Village, Nov 27, 1779; 055-002-a-0578; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 90)
      physical description: half sheet folded; d.s.
      dimensions: 37cm x 24cm
      Request for iron and rope. Addressed to John Fisher at Fish Kill Landing.
    - creator: Green, George place: Fish Kill, Nov 30, 1780; 055-002-a-0584; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 90)
      dimensions: 22cm x 7cm
      Receipt for axes to be delivered to John Fisher.
    - creator: Brill, Theodore place: Landing, Nov 6, 1780; 055-002-a-0577; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 90)
      Request for pileauger to transport clothing. Addressed to John Fisher and John Keefe.
    - creator: Nesbitt, Robert place: New Windsor, Nov 7, 1781; 055-002-a-0585; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 90)
      Request for candles and other items. Addressed to John Fisher at Fish Kill Landing.
    - creator: Sheafe, Henry place: Wapen Creek, Oct 12, 1781; 055-002-a-0583; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 90)
      dimensions: 19cm x 6cm
      Request for iron. Addressed to John Fisher.
    - creator: Hay, Udney place: Albany, Sep 18, 1778; 055-002-a-0576; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 90)
      Request for cable. Signed by Thomas Sichel and F. McMasters at Fishkill.
    - creator: North, Robert place: Kings Ferry, Sep 20, 1778; 055-002-a-0574; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 90)
      Account of supplies deliveres to John Fisher at Fish Kill Landing.
    - creator: Adams, Samuel, 1745-1819. place: White Plains, Sep 13, 1778; 055-002-a-0586; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 91)
      physical description: half sheet folded; a.l.s.
      To Sally Adams
    - creator: Adams, Samuel, 1745-1819. place: White Plains, Sep 7, 1778; 055-002-a-0587; 2 pages (Box 7, Folder 91)
      dimensions: 33cm x 21cm
    - creator: Adams, Samuel, 1745-1819. place: White Plains, Sep 7, 1778; 055-002-a-0590; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 91)
    - creator: Hardenbergh, Abraham. place: White Plains, Sep 9, 1778; 055-002-a-0591; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 92)
      Muster Roll of Colonel Goose Van Schaik's battalion. Signed by Abraham Hardenbergh.
    - creator: Woods, J. (Colonel of the 3rd Virginia Brigade) place: White Plains, Sep 9, 1778; 055-002-a-0592; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 93)
      dimensions: 35cm x 22cm
      To Joseph Swearingen.
    - creator: Haws, Robert. place: White Plains, Sep 11, 1778; 055-002-a-0593; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 94)
      Request for a furlough.
    - creator: McHenry, James, 1753-1816. place: [White Plains], Sep 15, 1778; 055-002-a-0594; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 95)
      To Colonel Palfrey. Washington to move from White Plains to Fredericksburg.
    - creator: Knyphausen, Wilhelm, Baron von. place: [New York], Nov 2, 1778; 055-002-a-0595; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 96)
      Pass for Anthony Archer of Westchester. Partly printed, signed by Robert Mackenzie.
    - creator: MacDougall, Alexander. place: Peekskill, Jan 6, 1779; 055-002-a-0596; 2 pages (Box 7, Folder 97)
      physical description: full sheet folded; d.s.
      Aaron Burr is authorized to impress teams.
    - creator: Hay, Udney. place: Fishkill, Feb 13, 1779; 055-002-a-0599; 2 pages (Box 7, Folder 98)
      physical description: full sheet folded; a.l.s.
      dimensions: 40cm x 34cm
      To Aaron Burr. Refers to letter from Washington and secret expedition to Long Island.
    - creator: Wyllys, George. place: Hartford, May 1779; 055-002-A-0602; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 99)
      Payment to Major Beebe for expenses during captivity.
    - creator: Neilson, John, 1745-1833. place: Elizabethtown, New Jersey, May 30, 1779; 055-002-A-0603; 1 pages (Box 7, Folder 100)
      Extract of letter by Neilson reporting on men impressed into service from White Plains.
    - creator: Scott, John Morin, 1730-1784. place: Fishkill, May 31, 1779; 055-002-A-0604; 3 pages (Box 7, Folder 101)
      physical description: half sheet folded, mounted on paper frame; a.l.s.
      To Governor Clinton with draft of Clinton's reply.
    - creator: Reed, Joseph, 1741-1785. place: Philadelphia, Jun 1, 1779; 055-002-A-0608; 4 pages (Box 7, Folder 102)
      dimensions: 38cm x 24cm
      Reports on the enemy presence in White Plains.
    - creator: Clinton, Henry, Sir, 1738?-1795. place: Headquarters, Philipsburgh, Jun 18, 1779; 055-002-A-0613; 5 pages (Box 7, Folder 103)
      physical description: full sheet, folded and sewn to additional half sheet.; a.l.s.